Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series CV. 1951 CONVENTION RESOLUTIONS
  - Sub-Series 517-124. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 124
    - Dispense with System, District and Terminal Boards of Adjustment Annual Meetings if financial conditions do not permit, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 125)
  - Sub-Series 517-125. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 125
    - Grand President to endeavor to devise ways to permit employee participation in insurance plans giving sickness, accident, hospital and surgical benefits at least cost, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 126)
  - Sub-Series 517-126. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 126
    - Secure increase in wages; double-time for Sunday work; paid holidays; longer vacations; sick leave, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 127)
  - Sub-Series 517-127. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 127
    - Rules changes for Railway Express Agency, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 128)
  - Sub-Series 517-128. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 128
    - 5 days' vacation after 1 year's service to 10 days after 5 years; 1 additional day for each year after 12 years, with a maximum of 30 days, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 129)
  - Sub-Series 517-129. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 129
    - Seek immediate cost-of-living bonus in Canada; limit period to complete negotiations of new agreement to 90 days; make union dues payable by all employees who benefit by increased wage, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 130)
  - Sub-Series 517-130. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 130
    - 1 additional day's vacation for each year after 15 years' service, maximum 30 days, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 131)
  - Sub-Series 517-131. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 131
    - Uniform wage scales, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 132)
  - Sub-Series 517-132. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 132
    - National Sick Leave Rule based on present vacation rules with cumulative benefits up to 5 years, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 133)
  - Sub-Series 517-133. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 133
    - Straight-time pay for holidays not worked; time and one-half pay when worked, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 134)
  - Sub-Series 517-134. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 134
    - Amend Railway Labor Act to provide that negotiations must be concluded in 8 days from time notices are filed, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 135)
  - Sub-Series 517-135. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 135
    - System Boards of Adjustment required to meet in cities served by carrier, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 136)
  - Sub-Series 517-136. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 136
    - Revise Railway Express Agency Rules, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 137)
  - Sub-Series 517-137. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 137
    - Union Shop, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 138)
  - Sub-Series 517-138. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 138
    - Class II employees to be paid for 7 legal holidays, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 139)
  - Sub-Series 517-139. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 139
    - Class II employees to receive 2 weeks' vacation with pay after 5 years' service; 3 weeks after 10 years, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 140)
  - Sub-Series 517-140. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 140
    - 10% differential for night work, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 141)
  - Sub-Series 517-141. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 141
    - Company to pay for union representatives for policing Agreement, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 142)
  - Sub-Series 517-142. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 142
    - Secure more liberal free transportation for Railway Express Agency employees, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 143)
  - Sub-Series 517-143. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 143
    - 10% wage differential for work after 9:00 pm, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 144)
  - Sub-Series 517-144. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 144
    - 3 week's vacation with pay for employees with 25 years' service, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 145)
  - Sub-Series 517-145. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 145
    - Liberalization of free pass privileges; no restrictions to employees with 25 years' service, 1951-1952 (Box 621a, Folder 146)
  - Sub-Series 517-146. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 146
    - Soo Line System Board of Adjustment to inaugurate negotiations to acquire rule granting employees paid holidays, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 147)
  - Sub-Series 517-147. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 147
    - Amend Retirement Act to reduce retirement age of male employees to 60, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 148)
  - Sub-Series 517-148. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 148
    - Amend Unemployment Insurance Act to liberalize benefits, 1951-1952 (Box 621a, Folder 149)
  - Sub-Series 517-149. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 149
    - 3 weeks' vacation after 10 years' service; National Sick Leave Rule; equalize rates of pay on all roads; retirement age of 60, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 150)
  - Sub-Series 517-150. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 150
    - National Holiday Agreement, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 151)
  - Sub-Series 517-151. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 151
    - 15 days' sick leave; amend Unemployment Insurance Act to eliminate 7-day waiting period, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 152)
  - Sub-Series 517-152. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 152
    - Secure guarantees that Brotherhood has jurisdiction over all freight entering or leaving freight house or train depot, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 153)
  - Sub-Series 517-153. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 153
    - Retirement annuity to be based on earnings of five highest years at half pay and 30 years of service regardless of age, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 154)
  - Sub-Series 517-154. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 154
    - Compulsory retirement at age 65 or with 30 years' service at least with $100 per month minimum, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 155)
  - Sub-Series 517-155. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 155
    - Double-time over regular basic rate to be paid if employee required to work during vacation period, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 156)
  - Sub-Series 517-156. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 156
    - Payment of all earned vacation time upon termination of employment, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 157)
  - Sub-Series 517-157. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 157
    - Revise National Vacation Agreement to provide 1 additional day vacation for each year after 10 years' service, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 158)
  - Sub-Series 517-158. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 158
    - Revise National Vacation Agreement to provide credit for armed service employees for any year or part thereof, after his induction into service the same as if that employee had rendered the required service to the carrier, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 159)
  - Sub-Series 517-159. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 159
    - Employee to be paid time and one-half if required to work his regular vacation, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 160)
  - Sub-Series 517-160. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 160
    - Revise National Vacation Agreement to provide for payment of all earned vacation time upon the death of an employee, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 161)
  - Sub-Series 517-161. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 161
    - National Holiday Agreement providing pro-rata pay for 7 holidays if employees are not worked, double-time pay for employees required to work, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 162)
  - Sub-Series 517-162. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 162
    - Worship Day to be known as Brotherhood of Railway Clerks Worship Day, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 163)
  - Sub-Series 517-163. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 163
    - If member makes contribution to Railway Labor's Political League in the equivalent of one month's dues, Lodge may waive their share of per capita tax, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 164)
  - Sub-Series 517-164. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 164
    - Uniform wage rates, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 165)
  - Sub-Series 517-165. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 165
    - Organize Bus Line employees and place under provisions of Railway Labor Act, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 166)
  - Sub-Series 517-166. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 166
    - Pay for all holidays not worked; double-time pay when worked; double-time for all work performed on Sundays, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 167)
  - Sub-Series 517-167. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 167
    - 1 day's vacation for each year's service over 10 years; vacations to be figured on seniority rather than compensated service, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 168)
  - Sub-Series 517-168. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 168
    - Adjust existing rates of pay on each system to highest rate paid for class of work performed, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 169)
  - Sub-Series 517-169. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 169
    - Negotiate Sick Leave Agreement providing 5 days' sick leave after 1 year's service, 10 days after 3 years; sick leave to be accumulated up to 30 days' leave per year, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 170)
  - Sub-Series 517-170. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 170
    - Retirement at age 60 or after 30 years' service; increase widow's or survivors' annuity, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 171)
  - Sub-Series 517-171. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 171
    - Oppose separate pension system for Grand Lodge officers and other officers, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 172)
  - Sub-Series 517-172. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 172
    - Revise National Vacation Agreement concerning furloughed or extra employees, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 173)
  - Sub-Series 517-173. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 173
    - Oppose legislation permitting construction of conveyor belt, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 174)
  - Sub-Series 517-174. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 174
    - Revise Express Agreement in connection with vacations for Express Messengers, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 175)
  - Sub-Series 517-175. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 175
    - Employees with 2 or more years' service to be granted unrestricted passes on foreign lines, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 176)
  - Sub-Series 517-176. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 176
    - Liberalize free transportation pass privileges, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 177)
  - Sub-Series 517-177. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 177
    - 5 days' vacation after 1 year's service to 15 days after 15 years; thereafter 1 additional day for each year's service with a maximum of 30 days' vacation, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 178)
  - Sub-Series 517-178. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 178
    - Disabled employees to receive not less than 50 per cent of regular weekly wage from Workmen's Compensation, 1951-1952 (Box 621a, Folder 179)
  - Sub-Series 517-179. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 179
    - Employees to be paid at least once in every 14-day pay period, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 180)
  - Sub-Series 517-180. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 180
    - 3 weeks' vacation for all members; paid holidays, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 181)
  - Sub-Series 517-181. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 181
    - Institute national movement to incorporate pass rights into existing Rules Agreement, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 182)
  - Sub-Series 517-182. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 182
    - Elect System Board Officers by referendum, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 183)
  - Sub-Series 517-183. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 183
    - 5 days' vacation for 1 year's service to 15 days for 5-15 years; thereafter 1 additional day vacation each year with a maximum of 30 days, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 184)
  - Sub-Series 517-184. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 184
    - Stores Department to make deliveries of supplies to Using Department, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 185)
  - Sub-Series 517-185. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 185
    - Liberalize free transportation pass privileges, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 186)
  - Sub-Series 517-186. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 186
    - Health and Safety, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 187)
  - Sub-Series 517-187. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 187
    - Equalization of wage rates; night differential; 3 weeks' vacation after 15 years' service, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 188)
  - Sub-Series 517-188. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 188
    - 5 days' vacation for 1 year's service to 15 days for 5-15 years; thereafter 1 additional day vacation each year with a maximum of 30 days, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 189)
  - Sub-Series 517-189. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 189
    - Revert Railway Clerk to magazine format, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 190)
  - Sub-Series 517-190. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 190
    - Consolidations, coordinations, and abandonments, 1951-1953 (Box 621a, Folder 191)
  - Sub-Series 517-191. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 191
    - 5 days' vacation for 1 year's service to 15 days for 5-15 years; thereafter 1 additional day vacation each year with a maximum of 30 days, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 192)
  - Sub-Series 517-192. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 192
    - Company to pay full-time for time employee serves as juror, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 193)
  - Sub-Series 517-193. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 193
    - Company to pay half cost of hospital and medical insurance for employees and their families, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 194)
  - Sub-Series 517-194. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 194
    - 10 working days' vacation for 1-10 years' service; thereafter 1 additional day for each year with a maximum of 30 days, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 195)
  - Sub-Series 517-195. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 195
    - 6 days' sick leave after 1 year's service, accumulative to 30 days, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 196)
  - Sub-Series 517-196. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 196
    - Canadian Railway Retirement Act, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 197)
  - Sub-Series 517-197. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 197
    - Secure agreement providing for pay for 7 legal holidays and in addition thereto include Election Day in a Presidential election year, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 198)
  - Sub-Series 517-198. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 198
    - Vacations based on seniority and length of service; sick leave with pay, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 199)
  - Sub-Series 517-199. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 199
    - Retirement at age 60 with 30 years' service, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 200)
  - Sub-Series 517-200. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 200
    - When retired because of disability, employee to receive $150 per month disability annuity without penalty, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 201)
  - Sub-Series 517-201. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 201
    - Reduce retirement age to 60; increase retirement pay to offset increased living costs, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 202)
  - Sub-Series 517-202. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 202
    - Retirement after 30 years' service, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 203)
  - Sub-Series 517-203. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 203
    - Retirement at age 60 after 30 years' service, 1951-1953 (Box 621a, Folder 204)
  - Sub-Series 517-204. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 204
    - Retirement after 30 years' service regardless of age, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 205)
  - Sub-Series 517-205. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 205
    - Increase benefits under Railroad Retirement Act, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 206)
  - Sub-Series 517-206. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 206
    - Pay for 7 legal holidays; time and one-half if required to work, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 517-207. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 207
    - Uniform wage rates, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 517-208. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 208
    - Additional vacation allowance for employees with 10 or more years' service, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 517-209. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 209
    - Sick leave based on years of service, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 517-210. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 210
    - Express Board of Adjustment to be recreated, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 517-211. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 211
    - Consolidations, coordinations, abandonments or dissolutions of existing facilities, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 517-212. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 212
    - Payment of all earned vacation time upon termination of employee's service, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 517-213. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 213
    - Employees with 10 years' service to receive 15 days' vacation; 20 days for 20 years, 1951-1952 (Box 621b, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 517-214. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 214
    - Revise Sick Leave Agreements to provide that if any portion of sick leave allowance is not taken in current year, same may be accumulated to a total of 30 days, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 517-215. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 215
    - Revise Rules Agreement concerning violations, Railway Express Agency, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 517-216. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 216
    - Amend National Vacation Agreement to provide that employee shall be paid time and one-half if required to work during scheduled vacation period, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 517-217. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 217
    - Secure pay for holidays; work on holidays to be paid at two and one-half times regular rate, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 517-218. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 218
    - Good Friday to become holiday, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 517-219. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 219
    - Extend escalator clause to pensioners, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 517-220. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 220
    - More effective and prompter handling of grievances, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 517-221. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 221
    - 15 days' vacation for 10 years' service, 20 days for 20 years, Railway Express Agency, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 517-222. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 222
    - Uniform wage scales, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 517-223. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 223
    - Secure more liberal free transportation pass privileges, Railway Express Agency, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 517-224. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 224
    - Negotiation of Sick Leave Rule for employees of Railway Express Agency, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 517-225. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 225
    - Safety measures; heaters in refrigerator cars, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 517-226. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 226
    - Honor Roll for Brotherhood members, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 517-227. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 227
    - Highway Motor Transportation Division to be established within the Grand Lodge, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 517-228. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 228
    - Waterway projects, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 517-229. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 229
    - Trucks and highways, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 517-230. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 230
    - Reciprocal Trade Agreements Extension, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 517-231. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 231
    - Millionaire's Amendment, 1951-1954 (Box 621b, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 517-232. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 232
    - St. Lawrence Seaway, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 517-233. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 233
    - Repeal Taft-Hartley Act, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 517-234. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 234
    - Importation of foreign labor into the United States for agricultural purposes, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 517-235. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 235
    - Retirement at age 60 after 30 years' service; 3 weeks' vacation after 10 years' service; National Sick Leave Agreement, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 517-236. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 236
    - Establish scholarships as memorial to pioneer members and members who gave their all for the principles of justice, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 517-237. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 237
    - Trucks and highways, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 517-238. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 238
    - Communism, Fascism and Nazism, 1951-1955 (Box 621b, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 517-239. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 239
    - Unsafe, unfit Express equipment, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 517-240. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 240
    - Legislative Committees in small states, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 517-241. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 241
    - Highway motor transportation, motor terminals, 1951-1952 (Box 621b, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 517-242. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 242
    - Punitive wage rates for overtime, Sunday and holiday work, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 517-243. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 243
    - Elimination of short-hour work, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 517-244. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 244
    - Health and safety, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 517-245. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 245
    - More effective and prompter handling of grievances, 1951-1954 (Box 621b, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 517-246. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 246
    - No discrimination against women employees, 1951-1955 (Box 621b, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 517-247. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 247
    - Better cooperation and coordination of efforts of Local Lodges and System Boards of Adjustment, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 517-248. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 248
    - Establish more uniform wage scales, 1951-1955 (Box 621b, Folder 43)
  - Sub-Series 517-249. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 249
    - Consolidations, coordinations, abandonments, or dissolutions of existing facilities, 1951 (Box 621b, Folder 44)
  - Sub-Series 517-250. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 250
    - Excepted or personal office force positions., 1951-1955 (Box 621b, Folder 45)
  - Sub-Series 517-251. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 251
    - Appeals to Grand President, Grand Executive Council and Grand Lodge Convention, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 517-252. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 252
    - Air Transport Industry Organization, 1951-1952 (Box 622a, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 517-253. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 253
    - Our Organizing Campaign, 1951-1952 (Box 622a, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 517-254. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 254